Software Engineer

Email: softluster4753@gmail.com

Mobile: +82-10-3023-6720

Summary

An all-around player with extensive experience in various fields. Expert in web server back-end development, particularly in the billing domain, but also proficient as a web front-end developer using React with JSX or TypeScript. Have a full-time master's degree in natural language processing, fully funded with preferential treatment from Samsung Electronics. Previously developed bootloader and device driver as a system engineer in the BSP team.

Programming Skills

- Languages: Java, SQL, Shell script, Terraform HCL, Javascript (+ JSX, Typescript), HTML/CSS, Python, C/C++
- Tools: Spring (MVC, WebFlux, JPA, Security), AWS (+ ECS, EKS), SoapUI, MySQL, React, PyTorch, HuggingFace, GGML
- Others: RESTful API, HTTP, TLS, Oauth 2.0, OOP/OOAD/DDD, Clean coding, TDD, Agile development (XP & Scrum), PCI-DSS (+ 3DS2), Device driver, Jira/Confluence, Git/SVN

EXPERIENCE

Task Oriented Dialog Research — Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd.

Suwon, Korea

Staff Engineer

Mar 2024 - Present

o On-device Virtual Assistant

Sentence Representation Learning Research — Hanyang University

Seoul, Korea

Researcher

June 2022 - Feb 2024

- Analyze and develop efficient methodologies for learning high-quality sentence representations based on large-scale language models
 - Published Hyper-CL: Conditioning Sentence Representations with Hypernetworks
 - Published Comparison and Analysis of Unsupervised Contrastive Learning Approaches for Korean Sentence Representations

Billing development — Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd.

Suwon, Korea

Engineer

Nov 2016 - March 2022

- o Led CP portal redevelopment: Used React, Spring MVC, Spring Boot, JPA (2020 2022)
- Developed DSA agreement (2021)
- Developed subscription product change for active subscription (2021)
- o Implemented 3DS2 respond to EU PSD2 law regulations (2020)
- Developed remote login to Samsung Smart TV using smartphone (2020)
- o Developed integration test framework: Used SoapUI, Groovy (2019)
- o Migrate buyer portal from monolithic to MSA: Used AWS ECS, Terraform HCL (2019)
- $\circ\,$ Rearchitect Billing service for PCI-DSS (2018)
- o Led buyer portal redevelopment: Used React, Spring Boot, JPA (2018)

BSP development — Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd.

Suwon, Korea

Engineer

Feb 2015 - Nov 2016

- o Port ramdump feature to Samsung Smart TV Kernel (2016)
 - Contributed to kexec-tools utility (https://bit.ly/3yG44df)

Samsung Software Membership

Suwon, Korea

Undergraduate

Feb 2013 - Feb 2015

- $\circ\,$ Modify Android Kernel to operate smartphone as webcam, speaker, microphone
 - Accepted as the best project of the year (http://bit.ly/358b7O8)

EDUCATION

Hanyang University

Master of Science in Computer Science; GPA: 4.06/4.5

Seoul, Korea

Mar 2022 - Feb 2024

Hongik University

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering; GPA: 3.5/4.5

Seoul, Korea Mar 2008 – Feb 2015

Publications

- Young Hyun Yoo, Jii Cha, Changhyeon Kim and Taeuk Kim, Hyper-CL: Conditioning Sentence Representations with Hypernetworks, *The 62nd Annual Meeting of the Association for Computational Linguistics* (ACL 2024).
- Young Hyun Yoo, Kyumin Lee, Minjin Jeon, Jii Cha, Kangsan Kim, and Taeuk Kim, Comparison and Analysis of Unsupervised Contrastive Learning Approaches for Korean Sentence Representations, *The 34th Annual Conference on Human and Cognitive Language Technology* (HCLT 2022).

Additional information

• Languages

o English: Proficient, Korean: Native